Guadalupe Lacombe

Email: gr_lacombe@hotmail.com

Mobile phone: 0272819733



PROFILE

I am in New Zealand with a Working Holiday Visa. I arrived to New Zealand 1st April and I will be in the country for at least a year, willing to work as much as I can. I am a hardworker and I am always ready to learn something now. I got my degree in Environmental engineer in 2017 and I worked in the city hall's environmental department for a year (Argentina). I have worked in different bars and restaurants over the last years too.

Education

2018 Japanese Food Course, L'Ecole Institute, Argentina.

2017 Environmental Engineer, Fasta University, Argentina.

2016 Food Manipulation Certificate, Argentina.

Work Experience

Apr 2019 to Jun 2019	Packer and Grader, Trevelyan's Pack and Cool Ltd, Te Puke, New Zealand.
Jun 2019 to July 2019	Mandarine Picking and Kiwi Pruning, Gisborne, New Zealand.
Jan 2016 to Dec 2016	Administrative, Mar del Plata City Hall, Argentina.
Jan 2015 to Feb 2019	Chef in 'Baum Brewery', Buenos Aires, Argentina.
Feb 2014 to Dec 2014	Chef in 'La Criolla restó', Buenos Aires, Argentina.
Jan 2012 to Jan 2013	Chef in 'Sapore di mare', Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Languages

English, Spanish and Italian.

<u>Skills</u>

Strong experience with Computers, Corel Draw, Word, Excel, Power Point, Outlook and Internet.

Driving record, B1.

Own car.